doattend.com 2017-11-20

# Online Event Registration Service - DoAttend Privacy Policy and Disclaimer

## Privacy Policy and Disclaimer

Doattend values the privacy of our visitors and our members and takes many steps to protect their privacy. By visiting Doattend's website you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement.

**What this Privacy Statement Covers**  
This Privacy Statement covers Doattend's treatment of personally identifiable information (Personal Information) that Doattend gathers when you access Doattend website.

**Links to Other Sites**  
Doattend contains links to blogs and other websites that are not owned or controlled by Doattend. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites.

**Information Collection & Use**  
Doattend is the sole owner of information collected on Doattend website. We do not share or sell your information with anyone without your authorization or consent in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Statement.

**Registration**  
Doattend provides some features exclusively to its members. Our registration process requires you to provide Doattend with a valid email address as well as a username and password of your choice. 

**Minor's Privacy**  
We do not collect or maintain information on Doattend from those people we actually know are under 13 years old, and no part of any Doattend Site is structured to attract anyone under 13 years old.

**Communications from Doattend**  
Newsletters: If you choose to subscribe to our newsletter(s) we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Unsubscribe instructions accompany each email. 

**Service-related Announcements** : We will send you strictly service-related announcements on the rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if Doattend is acquired or an earthquake swallows our data center we might notify you with an e-mail. You may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive these announcements you have the option to deactivate your account. 

**Customer Service** : Based upon the Personal Information you provide us we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or by telephone in accordance with your wishes.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
We do not share any individual user information with any of our business partners or outside vendors without permission. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to (1) comply with the law; (2) enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; (3) or protect the rights, property or safety of Doattend, our employees, our users, or others.

**Security and Confidentiality**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
We provide you the opportunity to access and edit all of your Personal Information within our member profile page or by emailing Customer Support. Information collected for the membership process, if requested, will be deleted within 21 days from the Doattend. However, some Personal Information may need to be maintained if it is connected with billing information or as required by law. Users of Doattend are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party. 

You may opt-out of receiving our newsletter by following the instructions included in each newsletter or by contacting us by email, phone, fax, or postal mail. 

**Cookies**  
We store a small text file called a cookie on your computer to track session data and persist your login for your convenience. A session cookie expires when you exit your browser. A persistent cookie stays on your computer until it is deleted. You can remove persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your browser's "help" files. If you reject cookies you may still use Doattend.  
Some of our advertisers may use cookies on Doattend. We have no access or control over these cookies. This Privacy Statement covers the use of cookies by Doattend only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
This Privacy Statement is a living document. We will modify this document as we add new features to Doattend. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time. If we make material changes to our privacy policy we will post those changes to this Privacy Statement, the Doattend.com homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Contact Us. 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy please contact us.
